<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="teamHelp">
<![CDATA[
 <h1>HELP - TEAM SCREEN</h1>
<p>Touch <b>change team name</b> button to enter a new name for the current team.<br/><br/></p>
<p>
<b>TEAM SELECTION</b><br/>
Select the team lineup by touching any of the position buttons to get option to <b>enter 
new player name</b> or select from list of available players.<br/>
Repeat for each position.<br/>
To remove a player from a position, touch the button and choose option to <b>reset position
to number</b> or touch on an available player to swap them in.<br/><br/>
To change the name of an entered player or correct mistakes you need to delete them 
(menu option) and re enter the name.
</p>
<p>
<b>ADDITIONAL PLAYERS / SUBS</b><br/>
If you have more than 15 players it is best to enter all names before the start so that they 
can be swapped in as subs during the match. <br/>Add additional players by clicking on a position
button and choosing the <b>enter new player name</b> option. Repeat on the same button until 
all players on the panel are entered. Then touch on the position button again and swap back in
the original player selected.<br/><br/>
Touch <b>make substitution</b> to record a substituion in the list of match/stats events.
 You will be asked to select which player is coming off and then select player going on.
 (Note that the name of the player going on must exist on the team already i.e. their
 name must have been entered previously.) <br/><br/></p>
<p>Touch <b>reset team selection</b> to reset all positions back to a number.  Note that player 
names already entered are saved for reuse.</p>
</p> 
<p><b>Cards</b> - Any black/yellow/red cards recorded in <b>enter stats</b> in the <b>SCORES</b> screen will
be displayed here</p>
<p><b>Subs</b> - Substitutions made will be displayed here.</p>
<p>
<b>ACTION BAR MENU</b><br/>
<b>delete a player</b> - delete a player from the current team panel.<br/>
<b>create new team</b> - create a new team, you will be prompted for the team name.  Note that
the current team, players and team lineup are automatically saved and can be retrieved later.<br/>
<b>load a saved team</b> - retrieve a previously saved team, you can select the name from a list. Note that a team
loaded in the other team screen will not be available<br/>
<b>delete a team</b> - delete an existing team, you will be asked to select name from list.  Note that 
currently active teams can not be deleted.<br/>
<b>reset current team selection</b> - reset all positions back to a number.  Note that player 
names already entered are saved for reuse.<br/>
</p>

 
 ]]>
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="scoresHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>HELP - SCORES SCREEN</h1>
<p>
<b>TIMER SECTION</b><br/>
Touch <b>start/stop</b> button to control timer.<br/>
Touch <b>mins/half</b> button to set timer length.
<br/>
Touch <b>1st half</b> button to set period of match. Extra time can be selected.
<br/>
Touch <b>-</b> or <b>+</b> button to increment or decrement timer by 30 secs.
<br/>
Touch <b>mins/half</b> button to set timer length.
</p>
<p>
<b>SCORES SECTION</b><br/>
Team names can be changed by swiping to the <b>TEAM 1</b> or <b>TEAM 2</b> pages.<br/>
Touch no the <b>comment</b> field to enter any additional details such as location, competition, hashtags for tweets, etc.<br/>
Touch <b>goals or points</b> buttons to increase score.<br/>
Touch <b>-</b> buttons to decrease score.
<br/>
Touch <b>enter stats</b> button to get to stats recording screen.

</p>
<p>
<b>ENTER STATS</b><br/>
You can record 1, 2 or 3 stats items per event - touch one item from the blue section,
touch a qualifying item from the pink section and touch an associated player from the green section. <br/>
Touch <b>OK</b> to complete entry and return to SCORES screen.
</p>
<p>
<b>MATCH EVENTS SECTION</b><br/>
The last four match events recorded in the ENTER STATS screen are displayed here. (Swipe to
the <b>STATS</b> screen to see the complete list of all match events.)<br/>
Touch <b>undo last stats entry</b> to delete last stats entry.
<br/>
Touch <b>reset all</b> to delete all stats events, reset timer and reset scores to zero.
</p>
<p>
<b>TWEET/TEXT SECTION</b><br/>
To send Tweets, you need to have the Twitter App, or equivalent, installed on your device and you must
be logged in.<br/>
For texts, your device must be capable of sending sms messages.  You can setup the number or numbers to send texts to in the 
<b>MENU</b> section.<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet score</b> or <b>text score</b> to send the current score. 
The contents (if any) of the <b>comment</b> field
will also be included.
<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet score + last</b> or <b>text score + last</b> to send the current score plus the last stats/match event entered. 
The contents (if any) of the <b>comment</b> field
will also be included.
<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet selected</b> or <b>text selected</b> to get a screen with a list of: comment, score, the last 10 stats/match 
event entered. Touch on the items you want to include in the tweet / text.  Note that tweets are limited to 140 characters 
so you will be limited to 3 or 4 items.
</p>
<p>
<b>ACTION BAR MENU</b><br/>
<b>setup texts</b> - enter the phone number to send sms texts to. You can enter more than one number, just use a comma to 
separate the phone numbers.<br/>
<b>reset timer</b> - reset timer to 0<br/>
<b>reset score</b> - reset score to 0<br/>
<b>reset stats</b> - delete all stats events and reset stats summary to 0<br/>
<b>reset all</b> - reset timer, scores, stats and delete comment<br/>
</p>
]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="reviewHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>HELP - REVIEW SCREEN</h1>
<p>
Summary of match stats is shown at top of screen.<br/><br/>
List of match/stats events recorded is displayed at the bottom of the screen. Swipe up/down
to scroll.
</p>
<p>
Touch <b>send all match data</b> to email all recorded match data including: team selections, score, stats summary, 
list of match/stats events recorded.
</p>



]]>
    </string>
    

</resources>